Come on, baby, [music and singing] take
a leap of faith.
We [music] got a love that's worth the
wait.
Darling, you've [music and singing] been
on
my mind.
Going to love [music] you till the end
of time.
And I know
>> [music]
>> you're the one.
Our story's [singing] just
>> Good morning, guys. I hope you're all
doing really well. I'm going for backlit
this morning because the window is so
bright, which you probably just saw from
me trying to do my hair. Very, very
quickly, my tailor man, tailor-er,
tailor man, tailor person is here this
morning. It's a guy guy I've used for
literally years. He tailors all my stuff
for me. He's absolutely incredible. I
have loads of pieces that need altering
for a very exciting shoot, which I'll
tell you guys about and that I've got
next week. So, I've got a huge pile of
stuff here that he is going to
tailor for me.
Mainly just trousers. Um I need the
lengths and the waists and stuff doing
of these trousers. He's literally just
arrived now. That was the doorbell for
him.
Um so, he will come up. I'll try them
on. He will tailor them.
I may try and vlog it a little bit if I
have the confidence. Probably won't. Um
also, how gorgeous are these pajamas, by
the way? I'm in love with them. They're
from Treats, and I think they could be
my favorite Treats pajamas that I've
worn in a long time. Let me show you.
I'm just obsessed with the color and the
little blue waistband. I mean, they're
very spring considering I'm about to go
into autumn, but I also got them in like
a gorgeous like bright baby pink.
But the fabric, this is like my favorite
PJ fabric ever. It's like soft buttery
cotton. Just so so nice. So, PJ of
choice anyway. He's literally going to
come up the stairs now. So,
first port of call for today is
tailoring appointment for this very
exciting shoot. Got my coffee.
Have a little sip. And then he's
probably waiting for me downstairs,
right?
>> Um is that where you would have it? On
the waist, yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I would. Yeah, I think that's
right. Oh, do you think it needs to be
But then it's going to like jack up,
isn't it?
>> Can see the shoes, I think, you know. If
any shorter, then it's going to be too
short, I think.
>> Yeah, do you think?
>> Yeah, I think.
>> They're way way way too long in the
rise. The waistband can come off and
then like go and be reattached. Cuz it's
like so much that needs I'll show you
when they're on.
>> That's okay.
>> But basically, yeah, they're just uh
>> Yeah, that's fine.
>> We want to keep them these.
>> We'll basically do everything original
and just drop it.
>> Right, okay.
>> That's okay.
>> Fine. All right, Barbara. I'll try these
on.
>> That's okay. No problem.
>> Yeah.
>> How about the pockets?
>> Well, ideally, there wouldn't be
>> Would you like
>> You can lose them if you want.
>> Yeah, if The only thing is because it's
being already, can't really remake it
unless this pocket starts from here.
>> Right. No, don't worry about the pocket.
The pocket can go.
>> Okay, we can just close it then.
>> Yeah, so that's basically it's two rolls
of the waistband.
And then the length is actually perfect
really. The length doesn't So, with the
waistband, normally cuz I've got a
parking ticket. Cuz they want to get me
catch my parking ticket.
I don't know if they made me feel too
bright or too short. I don't know. I
don't
>> Just just walk again because it's wider
than you know.
>> I I need them to You need to be able to
see the trainer otherwise they're going
to be female. So, that's all for the
shoes. So, that's priority. I mean,
there's only I think they're only going
to do one pair of these.
Perfect. Thank you so much.
>> [music]
>> Right. I just wanted to wait till you
got out the car cuz I got stage fright
of my own partner. Obviously, 10 years
into doing YouTube, I'm still I still
can barely vlog in front of it. I can
sometimes, other times I just can't.
Anyway, we've just pulled up to the
Trafford Centre really quickly because
Bambi just absolutely loves it here.
Like mother, like daughter. And we just
want to yeah, to take her out this
morning. We have someone at home helping
us with Majesty this morning. He's just
having his morning nap. So we thought
we'd get out of the house.
He's laughing [laughter] at me.
Um so yeah, we're just going to have a
little wander around. Maybe just get her
a couple What?
Where's your blow?
>> I've got a scan to do.
>> Yeah. Oh, it has to come in with the
angle of his arm like that.
>> Get a few bits, get some food, go home.
That's the plan today.
>> Right, perfect. Hang on, taggies.
>> You got it, taggies.
>> Taggies is my job. What a gorgeous day.
Do you know on Thursday, Tommy, it's
meant to be 32°?
We can get the paddling pool out, yeah.
How's it work? I've never done this new
thing before.
>> Oh.
>> That's so much better.
>> Apparently you just scan your app.
>> Oh my goodness, this is a red sparkly
one.
That's so cool.
>> Oh, I download an app.
>> Oh, that's so long. Beep beep.
Coming through.
Beep beep.
And then?
You press the button.
Baby's going TO GET A PLAIN CROISSANT
and just this, please.
Do you want to drink that, baby?
How funny. We just got some strawberries
from Pret and this one's shaped like
lips.
Look at that, babe.
>> Huh?
>> Look at the strawberry.
>> What is it?
>> It's a strawberry.
>> Oh.
>> How weird.
I've never ever seen a strawberry like
that in my life.
Do you want it or can I have it?
>> Me.
>> You'd like it.
Mhm.
Enjoy. Oh, kissy lips. Muah.
>> [music]
>> Come on, baby. [music] What you waiting
for?
You [music] and me could be
>> Apparently, I'm having a complete and
utter hot flash. Um, my cheeks are
literally doesn't look it on camera, but
they're so red. It's my house, so maybe
the heating's like flicked on because
it's gone a bit cooler. It's raining
outside. I'm actually currently looking
at a rainbow. Let me try and show you
guys. I don't think you'll be able to
see. Oh, no, you can see. Yeah, it's
just been raining, but it's not sunny,
so I don't know why there's a rainbow
out. Also, I know you're actually
technically meant to leave this in the
fridge, not the freezer, but the fridge
doesn't make it cold enough for me.
Like, I need it to be quite literally
ice cold, and the freezer does that.
Phase two,
Wow. My dressing table has never looked
more, I'm just a girl. I've got
chocolate, an electric fan to try and
cool my face down. I've got an ice
roller. I've got scalp massages. I've
got a Stanley filled with ice. In fact,
it also says I'm just a mom cuz it's
also got baby monitors everywhere I
look. One thing I've said a lot recently
is that this time around postpartum, I'm
pouring into myself care cup. I'm
pouring into my cup in general more than
I did the first time around most
definitely. Like, I feel as though
first time around postpartum, I would
never even have just sat and actually
taken proper time to I don't know
actually. I Honestly, I'm going to be so
for real, I don't remember a lot of that
time. I don't really remember what I was
doing, what my name was, who I was, what
I was even, you know, like, was I even
on planet Earth? Probably not. I mean, I
don't think this is the main reason, but
I think maybe 10% of the reason as to
why I feel a bit more human and a bit
more me is because I really have taken
time when I can to make me feel like me,
and to do my self-care, and to treat
myself to a new bra or two or 20, which
I need to show you at some point. Doing
little girly things that just make me
feel like
I'm not just a mom. Like, flipping love
being a mom, but I also love being just
a girl. Like, I keep seeing these
TikToks where it's like,
"You're a mom 24/7, but when you get
into bed, you're just a 27-year-old girl
trying to figure it out." And I'm like,
"Yeah, like, hard relate." I'm being an
organized girly, and I'm thinking about
when the 6-month mark hits, and the hair
loss comes thick and fast, or quite
frankly, the opposite, thin and fast.
I've been thoroughly enjoying my hair
since I've got my extensions back in,
and I've really been upping my hair care
routine because I really do feel like it
pays off. And one thing that I should
have added There's a few things I should
have added to my five things that I
think are worth your money. Kérastase
hair products. So, say it louder for the
people at the back. Kérastase hair
products. Listen, it's not the cheapest
form of hair care. It's definitely a
treat when it comes to hair care, but do
I think it's worth it? 110%. I genuinely
don't feel like my hair has ever looked
better, really, especially, obviously,
not since [laughter] having my color put
back on. The product I actually wanted
to show you guys tonight is something
that my sister put me on to. Zoë told me
about this product when she was going
through a bit of a weird phase with her
hair. She just noticed that her hair was
basically falling out, and it was really
thinning around the front. And so many
people recommended this product to her,
and then then she's gone on to recommend
it to me because she loves it so much.
From their Genesis range, and it's the
anti-hair fall fortifying serum. Don't
try and say that quickly. This is
something I've now added into my routine
probably for about the last just over a
month, and I am loving the results so
far. I know I'm not going to get hit
with the proper postpartum hair loss
till I'm probably about 6 months, like I
say. I'm going to do what I can to put
myself in best stead for when that does
come. It's basically just amazing for
hair fall and for strengthening your
hair, which postpartum is something that
I desperately need. Pop a couple of
pipettes into my scalp and then massage
it in. And luckily, I've tried and
tested it so many times now, it doesn't
make my hair greasy because as you guys
know,
I am the epitome of a greasy hair girly,
but luckily it's a really like
lightweight formula. It doesn't feel
heavy. I actually like to take a little
scalp massager and just massage it into
my roots just to really get it in there
and work it in. For the proper front
bits, I like to pop the last pipette
into my hand and just rub it in.
Just to sort of lightly put it in around
the area where postpartum hair loss
really, really gets you, which is kind
of right around the front. This product
literally completely changed always
hair, so I really do feel like if I stay
consistent with it, I'm hopefully not
going to get hit with the hair loss as
much this time. I'm going to go ahead
and dry my hair now even though it's
basically dry at this point. Like, how
hot is this house? I don't understand
what's going on.
My gosh, I'm having a hot flash. Anyone
would think I'm literally pregnant again
to be fair. I've just been drying my
hair, but I've been hot all evening. I
think I had my shower too hot. I think
that's what the problem is. I wanted to
show you how dry my scalp looks and how
clean my scalp looks after applying the
serum because as you know, if anyone's
going to get greasy hair from using a
product, it's going to be me. My love
for the Kerastase hair products just
grows and grows. I'm yet to find and use
a product of theirs that I don't like
and love and it stay in my routine
consistently. I'm pretty sure Kerastase
are going to give me a code
to get some money off at checkout. If
they are going to give me a code, I'm
going to pop it on the screen here for
you guys to use via Lookfantastic. I'm
pretty sure Mylo's okay because Tommy's
been in there with him and I've not been
called in and I've not been needed. It's
half term right now, so I've got half an
hour until his next bottle. I will catch
up with you guys in the morning. Night.
>> Is that a is it Canon?
>> It's a Canon. I never use Canon.
>> You always use Sony.
>> I always use Sony.
>> Sony?
>> Sony.
>> [laughter]
>> Sony, there's
>> So, if you comment at the day saying
that why does Molly talk so much like
Tommy now?
>> Maybe that's because she's been around
Tommy every single day for the past 10
years.
>> I actually have lived in Manchester now
for 10 years.
>> What do you mean to speak like me cuz
for me to hear you speak, I would say
that your comparison to me, you speak
very posh.
>> Basically, I think when I add things
like like on the end of sentences or
>> Yeah, what is
>> I I put the accent on on purp- I put I
put the accent on purpose sometimes.
Anyway, I've given absolutely no contest
I'm going to do it when you're out the
room cuz I'm going to get so embarrassed
doing this part of the video because I
just do get embarrassed.
>> I won't be embarrassed if I open my
mouth.
>> Keep me to get a child with you.
>> Mhm.
No, I can still hear you.
>> Well, come on. I can't hear you.
>> Yes, you can hear me.
>> What?
>> You smell like ass.
>> [laughter]
>> I can hear you laughing. Right, let me
explain. Same pajamas, just a different
country. So, yes, I started off the vlog
in these pajamas and this part of the
vlog I'm wearing these pajamas, but I'm
in a whole different country. Not really
sure why why that's relevant at all.
But, I have quite a bit to update you
on. I am in Dubai. We are here for
basically a day. I had to come out here
for something to do with work and I was
going to come out by myself. The most
flying visit ever. You know what I mean
when you say flying visit? Is it fly in
or flying? Fly in, I think it is. I
wasn't going to vlog, but I kind of
thought to myself, I've been at home so
much in my my over the last few months
obviously with pregnant and having a
baby. I'm going to be at home moving
forward, like going into cozy season,
like we're not really going to be going
anywhere. So, I kind of thought it might
be nice to actually vlog whilst away.
And I don't know.
Just the the one day that we're here,
bring you guys along for it and show you
I don't know anything that we got to and
we got here yesterday afternoon and had
a little bit of chill time and honestly,
we didn't know what to do with
ourselves. Like this has actually made
even though we've only been we arrived
and came here yesterday afternoon, it
just made me appreciate yesterday
afternoon coming away with Bambi.
Obviously, it's different with minus cuz
he's so young, but coming away with kids
is actually so much more fun than coming
away without them because we literally
were just twiddling our thumbs around
the pool. Like I didn't know what to do
with myself and
I don't know what's happened to me. Like
am I becoming like a wholesome mom
because I actually do love some baby
free time sometimes, like kid free time.
Like that I'll be so honest, like I do
love it, but
I I didn't I didn't love it yesterday. I
was like oh, I felt really happy. I was
like I just kind of
Yeah, I just wish that the kids were
here. And also like it is very like
minus is so young. Like ideally I
wouldn't have had to have even left him
at this point, but we're literally here
for less than 48 hours. So, got to get
this little work thing done that I've
got to do and then we're going to go
straight home. But anyway, I picked up a
new blogging camera yesterday. We went
to the mall for dinner and obviously
because when do we ever go anywhere
fancy when we're out here? And
basically, I went into this Virgin shop
and it's just like tech gadget shop.
It's unbelievable for like all kinds of
techy bits and I saw this new blogging
camera from Canon that came out last
year and I I'm quite obsessed with
cameras and like blogging equipment and
all that stuff and I always want my
footage to be the best it can be for you
guys. So, I thought I'll pick up a new
camera and we can try it out. I love
that you can fit so much in the screen.
Like I'm holding it quite close and look
how like
you can see so much. Um
Wow, this camera's good, guys. I think I
really like it. I actually tried it
yesterday cuz I tried to start this vlog
last night, but I was outside and my
lens kept steaming up, so I thought I'll
just start it tomorrow cuz it's um by
the way, it's 44° outside. Another
reason why we never ever normally come
at this time of year, and I'm cuz we
were actually got bubble diarrhea. We
were actually considering it turning
into a family holiday, and we were going
to bring the children out. Um and we
were going to make it like a fun thing.
Cuz I'm so so so glad that we didn't
because the heat is incredible. It's
44°.
Yesterday it was 44°, and
I think it's like the same today. It's
insane. I feel like old times with me
and Tommy and like our holiday vlogs
that we used to do.
They they used to be like 2 weeks, these
holidays we used to go on when we were
childless, but yeah, I just thought
I'm waffling now. We're actually staying
at a hotel that I've wanted to stay at
for ages. It's called the Massa Al Arab.
We normally stay at a hotel which I can
just see over there when we come on
holidays here, but I wanted to try this
hotel for a really long time, and I
actually personally think this hotel's
not very kid-friendly, like a kid vibe.
Um so I thought this would be the
perfect time to try it. I'm quite
impressed with it, to be honest. It's
very gorgeous. It's very modern. It's
brand new, and the views We actually
slept with the curtains open last night
and had that as our view, which was just
stunning. What to do with my hair?
Comb it down.
Standard.
Watch on.
My face got so burned when we were in
Athens, so I picked this SPF up at the
airport.
SPF 50 plus. I'll be so honest, like I
can be quite bad for remembering my SPF
sometimes.
It's not good. Um
so I
tried this one. This is La Roche-Posay.
It said invisible fluid, so I'm hoping
that
it will just
not leave a white cast or anything. I'm
just going to pop some serum on top.
Pedicure, obviously.
And then, obviously, this is a product
that I literally use pretty much every
single day now.
Rhode glazing mist. I absolutely love
this.
Right. Random outfit of the day. Black
Hunza G
x Burberry costume, which is cute.
Peppermayo
trousers, which are very low-waisted and
also hug my thighs quite a bit, which
I'm not sure if I like or not.
>> I like them.
>> Do you?
>> Yep.
>> And then, I didn't bring a black bag cuz
I don't actually really know what I
packed for this. Like, I've actually
packed really nothing appropriate. So,
I'm actually taking this
um the pouch that Frank got me, which I
do use as a wash bag, but I'm going to
kind of use it as like a a clutch cuz I
don't really need like my um
pool stuff in it and a charger and
stuff. So, yeah. Oh, and then I've got
my jelly Christopher Esber FitFlops on.
And then, a ponytail cuz obviously I had
a blow-dry before we left and after 1
day in 44° heat,
the blow-dry was no more. Oh, I forgot
to put deodorant on.
>> So, I'll pop it out.
>> You look really cute. Scent of the day,
Memory. Sun is up.
I need sunglasses. Um
All right, not that.
Looking gorgeous.
Wow. There he is.
>> Can I have your water?
That's a thumbnail, isn't it?
>> It's a bit dark, but good idea. Come
again.
>> So, if any of you are on trains out
there, it's horrible, isn't it? It's
like you get up and you just feel really
good but then an hour passes and you're
like
>> Ooh, I remember the first time I trained
in the morning. Ooh.
>> Trained every morning.
>> Pyrox friends.
>> [music]
>> Double parked. Triple parked, actually.
You can do a spot of light reading round
the pool. You Can't Hurt Me by David
Goggins.
>> There it is.
I seen it in the in the airport in
Greece when we was there.
>> Mhm.
>> But it was all in it was all in Greek. I
like David Goggins because he's extreme
and I see a lot of myself in him. So,
with that mindset of life and doing
something, there is no way that you
can't see it through. There's there's no
way.
>> And there's no way. Obviously, the man
is 10 times, million times fitter than
I'll ever be, but it's not about
fitness, it's about mind.
>> How? You look like the fittest person I
know.
>> Goggins is built different.
>> Babe, I'm not going to lie, I'm actually
really enjoying this camera.
>> Yeah? How much is it?
>> I'm really enjoying it.
>> Do you?
Mhm?
>> Ooh, we're getting filmed.
>> [laughter]
>> Some guy was just filming us.
Why are you walking down the street?
>> As light as day.
>> The light got better.
>> So, basically, we went to the
adults only pool yesterday.
And
what was it like, babe, the adults only
pool?
>> Absolute hell.
>> Well, it was just so quiet and quite
frankly
>> the adults only pool. It's a boring.
>> It is boring, isn't it?
>> I want to get smashed. I want to
hear a bit of laughter.
>> Yeah, but does that make us kind of
weird that we're going to go to probably
a kids pool when we don't have any kids
with us?
>> Got two.
>> Yeah, but they're not here.
>> We are kids ourselves.
>> To be fair, that that is true.
>> I've brought a book to read. I'm not
going to be able to read a page.
I'm going to flash about and feel like
I'm three years old.
Oh.
>> Cheers.
What a perfect day.
Nice.
>> Mhm.
>> We got Caesar salads.
Delicio. Mhm.
So good. Wow.
>> It's a pretty good nice background that.
>> What? Is it?
Oh, wow. Thank you.
Yeah?
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you, babe.
>> It was nice.
>> Yeah, my vagina's completely in it.
>> Of course it is, yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> That's when people say I sound like you.
Remember if I say like at the end of
something.
Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah.
>> Just dashed myself in the shower, had a
quick freshen up, and now I've actually
just managed to get myself a blow dry at
the hotel. So, I'm going to head
downstairs and just freshen myself up.
Anyway, I'm wearing the palm pants from
Maybelline, which are like my go-to
summer pant. And then this black
swimming costume, which is one of my
favorite swimming costumes ever. It's
actually from Free People, and Taylor
put me onto this swimsuit because it's
probably the most flattering
swimming costume. It is definitely an
investment piece. I think it is over 100
pounds a swimming costume. I want to say
it's like maybe like 100
120 pounds or something like that. It's
definitely not cheap for swimwear.
However, in my opinion, this is the only
black swimming costume you'll ever need.
It is so flattering. It has this kind of
like ruched detailing the whole way down
it.
Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
I go home tomorrow.
Literally a day.
Yeah, we got here yesterday.
Yeah, very quick.
Yeah,
I know, but I have two children at home
and one is very young. Also, I have to
get back
very quickly, yeah.
Yes.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you so much. You smashed it.
Huh?
You said yeah.
Thank you.
blow dry done. He actually did a really
good job. There's so much volume there,
which is literally going to last me all
of about I kid you not, probably about
30 seconds when I go outside because the
humidity is going to ruin this. He was
like, "Do you mind if I take a little
bit of content off it?" I was like, "Go
for it. I'm only doing the same here
anyway with my camera." I feel
like I've been a little bit better with
blogging in public, guys.
Don't you think? I've been actually
quite good this trip. I've been whipping
out my camera in
all kinds of places. I think it's I've
got a new camera.
I just want to use it and utilize it,
really, but
I'm happy with that blow dry.
Aw,
aw, bless you. I'll tell her I said
hello.
Aw.
Thank you. Aw, thank you so much. Thank
you.
>> What are these cameras?
>> [cough]
>> I've just choked.
I'm in shock.
>> [cough]
>> Guys,
he's fishing my gender out the pool.
Like I can eat the other chicken nugget
if the bird's
literal beak has been on the plate.
That's the question. Will I get some
sort of like bird disease? I'm just
whilst I talk to you guys, I'm just
going to cover up my food just so that
doesn't happen again. I feel like I
didn't react to that properly because
there was a few people watching me and I
got very embarrassed. Um,
but yeah, that just happened. Anyway, we
are back at the pool. I actually just
went and did a bit of shopping. I
treated myself to
a new necklace, which wasn't really on
the cards, but here we are. And then
I've just come back to the pool and a
bird just took a chicken nugget off my
plate, which might get over maybe never.
He's actually left a little bit of crumb
there. He's left a bit of a chicken
nugget there. Do you think it's fine for
me to eat the chicken nugget now that
his beak's been all over my food? That's
the question.
Went to the shops, I bought myself I
bought myself an apple, banana, and a
carrot. And I also bought myself a new
necklace, which is a bit of a treat. Um,
and obviously my blow dryer's now gone
to um,
ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
And apart from that, oh yeah, the reason
we came out to the pool was because
there's crows everywhere. When we were
leaving,
nah.
When we were leaving the pool earlier,
the guy was like, "Oh, you're leaving?"
Like we were just about to bring over a
surprise for you. We were like, "Oh my
gosh, like that's really sweet, but we
need to leave." And we were like, "We'll
come back at 5:00." So we came come back
at 5:00 and the guy that said he has a
little surprise for us appears to have
forgotten about the surprise. So, we
actually came back here for no reason,
but it's actually really nice anyway.
Saw a comment on TikTok earlier that
says, um,
"Tommy and Molly live near me and I see
them arguing all the time out in
public."
>> Next time you see us arguing,
>> [laughter]
>> just come in and say hi.
I would I would love to
>> us arguing, how about I film it and post
that? THAT'D BE PRETTY FUNNY.
>> [laughter]
>> THIS SIDE. ALSO, it's completely not
true.
>> Honestly, the only place that we can
argue
>> all the time. We argue constantly.
>> Baby, come on. We do fake argue quite a
lot.
>> Don't we? We do fake argue all the time.
Like, is that just a start? Is that just
a niche thing? What would an example of
a fake argument be?
>> Baby, you really do annoy me, don't you?
>> I'm just [laughter] saying I don't
>> She had good acting skills.
>> I just saw it. What should I do now? Go.
That was really good, babe. Well done.
>> See what I'm saying? Like,
>> Yeah. Oh, that was That was
That was hot.
>> Really?
>> No.
>> [laughter]
>> Gorgeous shot, by the way. You look
absolutely beautiful. Oh, should we tell
>> her not to get the picture?
>> Shall [laughter] we tell everyone about
the woman?
I already Also, also, also, can I just
say, truly, that's me.
>> see.
>> You say, "Where's the picture?"
>> the worst picture I've ever [laughter]
seen of me.
>> I think you look beautiful.
This man is so handsome that random
women come up to him and tell him how
handsome he is. We were outside the
reception and what did she say, that
woman?
>> Turned around and she said, and I went,
"Oh, hi." She went,
"You're so handsome."
And I said, "Thank you."
>> Thank you very much. Also, I was saying
to the guys earlier that the whole
reason we come up to the pool was for
the surprise that the guy said he had
for us at 5:00.
>> He had nothing.
>> Air tumbleweed.
>> No, no. In all honesty, I think I think
it was watermelon.
>> Right. He's back. He's back.
>> Good.
Watch it land on me back. Watch it land
on me back. I'm feeling
>> please, I really hope it does. But also,
what else is impressive is this camera.
I'm sorry. This camera might be the best
thing I've discovered this year, you
know.
>> It reminds me of a cruise ship. Tell me,
right, if that doesn't remind you of a
cruise ship.
>> Yeah, it does have I think it's based
off of a ship, you know. That's the kind
of energy it gives. Can I see?
Aw, don't say I'm already really
homesick. We're literally going home
tomorrow.
Aw, that is the cutest Bambi's going to
love that.
Aw, that is the cutest little thing.
>> What are these for?
>> It's a card.
>> Dear Molly and Tommy, I hope you're
enjoying your time at Marsa Al Arab and
making
the most of this special time together.
I know Bambi and Midas are waiting for
you back home. So, here is a little
something for you to take home to them,
a small reminder of your time with us.
Oh my gosh, they've got little our
initials on.
>> Nice, isn't it?
>> That's so cute. Aw, I love that. Now,
that makes up for the fact that they've
got your initials as
Tommy Fury.
>> [laughter]
>> And they brought my teeth.
>> Tommy Fury, I don't I don't know who
Tommy Fury is, but it ain't you.
I was going to film me doing a little
bit of makeup, but my camera's strobing.
That's the first thing it's done that's
upset me. I'm really, really enjoying
this camera. I feel like I love how much
of the shot you get in. Like, we'll do
this instead.
I'll come back to you with a little bit
of makeup on. Goodbye.
There we are.
Just felt like my cheeks were very rosy
because I'd caught the sun a little bit
today, so
that's a little [clears throat] bit
better. Also, the strobing's really
killing my vibe.
>> This is her 8 weeks post baby.
>> He's 10 weeks.
>> He's 10 weeks. So, I'm going to walk
away now.
>> It's okay.
What happened at the weirdest time,
right?
Because we've never, ever, ever not
known what we want to eat, ever, do we?
In the whole 7 years of us
being together, we've never been
indecisive about food.
>> Never.
>> We always know what we want to eat. But
tonight
>> It's not really
>> But we sat down in a restaurant and then
we started ordering. He said, "Oh, we
don't have that. Oh, we don't have
that."
>> the fellow tried to call the police on
me.
>> And then he tried to have a fight with
Tommy because he went, "Yeah, you've
already told me that." And then Tommy
said, "I don't want any bacon. Can I
have no bacon on my burger, please?" And
he went, "Yeah." And then Tommy was
like, "I'm just checking that there's no
bacon on the burger." He went, "Yeah,
you've already told me that." And Tommy
went
But what did Oh, right. He basically
spoke in gibberish and then he said he
didn't And then he said, "Do you want to
fight it?"
Dinner.
Oh, what are we doing here, babe? Should
we just go home?
>> What Manchester are we in?
>> Yeah. I've always wanted to try one of
these. It's a lettuce burger.
>> Yeah.
>> What do we think?
Is it lush?
>> I don't like tomatoes or pickles.
>> Well, I've not got either of that in
here.
It's good.
Mhm.
I like that.
I like the crunch with the meat.
>> You hung up on Daddy.
>> [laughter]
>> That's not funny.
>> She knows how to hang up on people now.
>> Give me Give me a kiss now. I love you.
>> [crying]
>> Mwah. Look, I've got I've got crumbs.
I've got crumbs.
>> In your hand?
>> I've got crumbs.
>> [laughter]
>> You see it? Feel that on the side. Just
touch it. Touch it on the side.
>> Oh my gosh, it's like a claw.
>> Oh my god. Ah.
>> No, no, no, no, no.
>> It's like a claw.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like a claw you get in the arcade
to grab something.
>> [laughter]
>> It's not going anywhere, feel it.
FEEL IT, WOMAN.
WHAT'S LIKE A CLUB?
You have fun with surprise.
>> I'm so ready to go home and see them.
>> That it is. No I didn't not worth it.
>> Yeah.
>> You just want to be with them?
>> I know.
>> And when you with them, you just want
nights like this.
>> You just want a minute. You always want
what you can't have. It's crazy. Oh my
goodness.
>> I said they must have put a Z equal pill
in their burgers. [laughter]
>> That lettuce burger was unreal. Also, we
got
>> Don't even class that as a burger. I'm
not even going to allow you to do
burgers injustice like that.
>> It was so good.
>> A burger.
>> I love the texture of the crunch on with
the meat.
>> of what? A leaf?
>> Yeah, but it was like a crunchy iceberg.
>> class a burger if it's between two buns.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, the state.
>> But I just wanted to take a opportunity
to show you guys our view.
Last night we slept with the curtains
open and we're doing the same again
tonight.
And it doesn't get much better than
that. I think this has been like one of
the highlights of our trip as well as
this view out the window.
Hello Thomas.
>> Hello Molly.
Everything okay?
>> Everything's fine, yeah.
How's your sushi? We got it at the
airport guys.
>> It's delightful.
>> We're feeling a little bit out of place
right now because we're in the first
class lounge and it's quite bougie.
Which is something that we are not.
We've been doing our peak and trough for
the last two days. It's something that
we like to do at the end of each trip
where you state your peak and your
trough.
Which means best bit and lowest bit.
My best bit was
quality time together.
Ice lattes were amazing.
I did really like the hotel.
And what was my other peak?
Just the laughs, funny times, quality
time together.
>> Laughed a lot on trip.
>> We always laugh. And then my trough was
that we had an argument on the first
day.
>> Why are you including that?
>> Because I was taking too long to get
ready and Tommy was angry. The minute
he'd been to the gym and eaten, we were
absolutely fine.
And that was my trough.
>> What was your peak? Above all the
laughs.
But all I can remember from this trip is
laughing.
>> We've had a lovely time.
>> Yeah, are you okay?
>> Yeah, can I take a picture with you?
>> Yeah.
>> Is that all right?
>> You wanted to disturb me.
>> No, it's fine.
>> I can take it.
>> Yeah, back home now. Yeah, you?
>> Oh yeah, I'm back to Switzerland.
>> Oh nice, Switzerland. I love it.
>> Oh, there you go.
>> You fancy some?
>> Yeah. So I'm trying some kunafa.
Actually, fun fact, I've never had Dubai
chocolate.
However, I can't decide if dark
chocolate or
>> I think it's in between.
>> Milk chocolate. I don't like dark
chocolate. Anyway, bottoms up. Do you
think you're going to like it? I don't
like pistachio.
>> Just put it in your gullet, will you?
>> I don't like pistachio. I don't think I
like it.
Oh, that's not for me at all.
>> Really?
>> Really nothing.
Do you want to try some?
>> Uh I'm all right, babe.
Kunafa is definitely not for me. I've
never had it before.
I don't like pistachio.
>> I don't like pistachio. I don't know why
I'm eating it, to be honest with
>> Do you want to just put it down?
>> Yeah.
I'm just a girl in the world.
>> Show them what's in your gullet.
There you go.
>> [laughter]
>> If you're not doing this, you get your
game up.
>> Babe, you don't always do that.
>> I always say hello.
>> Hello?
>> Apart from that time we got a picture
coming out the airport and I
>> [laughter]
>> But yeah, apart from that, I always say
hello.
>> I am dead.
>> Say hello. Thank you.
>> I can't believe you just brought that
up. That is the funniest thing.
Yeah, there was the one time this
picture went No, what was it? A video?
Picture or video? I can't remember.
I don't really know why, but I was just
basically carrying everything out of the
airport. And you What did you have?
You just have dinner in
>> No, sorry. TGI Fridays now.
>> Do you know one thing about me though?
I'm such a control freak in those kind
of situations. I I do kind
>> did snap.
>> Did I snap?
>> Yeah, you snapped.
And then I have to talk about stuff we
were having a massive argument as we do
always in public.
>> Always.
>> And
>> We probably were having an argument then
though.
>> You were having an argument with
yourself.
>> [laughter]
>> That sounds about right. Sorry.
George is probably having an argument
with suitcases. We are getting on the
plane now.
Oh, no.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll take some pajamas.
>> Yeah, so
the biggest size and the largest and the
medium.
Uh I love the large.
>> The large.
Thank you.
Pajamas, eh?
Pajamas.
>> I might as well answer. So, you're
getting your own clothes, aren't you?
Don't you?
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you so much.
>> It's like old times, isn't it?
>> It is, yeah.
>> It really does feel like old times.
Is it Yeah, we both aged horrendously.
No, I don't know. I thought you look
great. I feel like I still got a bit of
youth in me.
>> You think you look
Well, you do look pretty tasty.
>> What?
>> You look so tasty.
>> Stop it.
Babe.
Did you tell me he was coming?
>> What?
>> Did he even come in?
>> put them in your suitcase.
>> Darling. Oh, he
>> How was I meant to know you were coming?
>> Now, what?
>> So, it's the diamond demand service.
>> Hi.
Thank you so much.
Amazing. Thank you. Now, why did I put
these on my side and not on your side?
>> Your breath smells like engine.
>> That's actually probably all right.
Smells like petrol. I'll take that.
>> Hello.
Mouse. A big smile.
Oh.
Oh. Oh. Oh my goodness. And just like
that, we are home. New filming location
unlocked. I've never ever ever thought
to put my camera here.
My new camera. My new camera has made it
home and I think my new camera is here
to stay, guys. Honestly, I
I really really like it. I feel like I
just I know I keep saying this, but I
love how much
it gets in the shot. You can see much
better now
the artwork on the stairs. Let me just
It looks like that. I actually think it
looks really nice that.
Someone just had their first nap of the
day and the first nap of the day has
gone really well. He didn't need me to
resettle him at all, but
I don't [snorts] know. We actually were
home all day yesterday. This is Sunday
today and yesterday was a bit of a
interesting day with the naps. Honestly,
every day in this newborn not newborn
life anymore cuz he's not a newborn
anymore is just so
up and down. Like we'll we'll have one
really positive day and then one not so
positive day and then the next day will
look a bit better than the day after
that won't be so good. Like it really
just is total pot luck. Tommy's just
taken Bambi to his gym class with him,
which is
a new thing that he's trying. They've
got like a little
at his gym that he goes to. They've got
a tiny little like crash thing with a
baby gate on it. So, I think he's just
popped her in there.
Probably put Peppa Pig on his phone and
just absolutely winging it, but
like I say, we're really just having one
each at the minute just because that
works for us. And obviously we had some
lovely quality time together in Dubai,
so
feels a bit more bearable now to not be
together.
Cuz we had some good times together.
Yes. I'm just going to have a chilled
Sunday at home today. I'm hopefully
going to not go crazy with the
resettling cuz I do feel like
I spend my life when I'm at home these
days just in a dark room.
Oh, you okay? I just spend my days in a
dark room with him constantly resettling
him. I did kind of say this morning some
days I just feel like sacking the whole
routine thing off and just letting him
be one of those babies that just sleeps
when he needs to sleep and just
becoming more of a winging mom, but
actually then I just thought that's my
bad mood talking and it's not actually
the case at all. I do
Routine is life for me. But anyway,
we've been home for 5 seconds and I'm
already told you about routine. But
yeah, home now, back into the swing of
things. Quite literally.
Right into the flow. And I'm actually
got my first week back at work this
week. Um I've got a big shoot which I
never told you guys about. Um you know
when I had the fitting, I had no fitting
but like tailor appointment with my guy,
he um was tailoring all those clothes
for a shoot I have this week with
Adidas, which is very exciting. It's
kind of my first shoot back. I've
technically got my first shoot back
tomorrow with maybe. Um I'm doing
something small with maybe tomorrow.
That's kind of my first like warm-up
shoot, and then
yeah, this week I've got big shoot, big
campaign, which I won't say too much
about, but just know that
exciting things are coming with Adidas,
but I can't say much more I don't think.
If you made it to the end of this video,
guys, I love you millions. I'm going to
bring it to a close now cuz if I don't
bring it to a close now, it's going to
be one of those videos that probably
never ever makes it out for like another
2 weeks. And I'm being a little bit more
consistent with my videos at the moment
I feel like. I've done two videos and
I'm like, "Oh, I'm consistent again." If
you're watching this video, and
hopefully I will see you all in my next
one. Bye, guys.